<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="script.playlistcreator"
       name="Playlist [COLOR gold]C[/COLOR]reator"
       version="3.0.4a"
       provider-name="Tha [COLOR gold]G[/COLOR] Thang">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.mutagen" version="1.47.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Lightweight Playlist Generator</summary>
        <description lang="en">
            Generates Video Playlists.
            Specialized for diverse video collections, including non-standard media.
            Features include:
            - Folder and file scanning with various filtering options.
            - Advanced sorting (alphabetical, newest, custom).
            - Set management for reusable playlist configurations.
            - AI-powered filename cleaning, content grouping, and metadata enhancement (requires NLTK data download).
            - Context menu integration for direct playlist generation and stream saving/downloading.
            - Customizable playlist output with metadata and color tags.
        </description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
        <news>
            [3.0.4a]
            - Critical fix: Add-on now launches correctly without crashing.
            - Removed background service. Add-on now runs on demand.
            [3.0.3a]
            - Improved stability: Add-on settings now correctly reset after creating playlists or editing set settings, preventing unexpected changes.
            - Enhanced settings management: Editing set-specific settings is now smoother, ensuring all settings load correctly and use smart defaults.
            - General refinements for a better user experience in set management and playlist creation.

            [3.0.2]
            - **New possibilities with AI:** AI features now start faster and use fewer resources by loading smart tools only when you need them.
            - **Easier NLTK Data:** Simplified downloading of NLTK data (required for AI features) directly from add-on settings, ensuring it's always found.
            - Overall improvements to AI integration for smarter filename cleaning and content grouping.
        </news>
    </extension>
</addon>